Jamie Robertson

Full stack developer

hello.jamie@protonmail.com +44 (0) 7881 820 789

in LinkedIn profle linkedin.com/in/iamie-r/ I currently work as a consultant for Reason Studios (formerly Propellerhead Software), creators of Reason, a leading audio software used for producing, recording and editing music.

I have over five years of professional experience working with the Django framework for web development and the React JavaScript library.

Professional experience:

Reason Studios (formerly Propellerhead Software)

March 2014 – Present | Position: Developer

Responsibilities:

- Design & development of reasonstudios.com.
- Analysis and user segmentation based on engagement and behaviour.
- Marketing automation development, using Salesforce APIs.
- Infrastructure development, using Vagrant and Ansible.
- Development of internal analytics dashboards.

Monki

April 2013 - January 2014 | Position: Graphic design / Final art Responsibilities:

- Design for a range of material for print and web.
- Development of online campaigns for monki website.
- Design & development of internal sites to be used by store employees.

Bright Young Things Tuition (consultant)

September 2012 - March 2013 | Position: Mobile app design / development Design & implementation of educational mobile apps.

Craftsman Websites

January 2012 - August 2012 | Position: Web design / development Projects included the 'Notting Hill Carnival App' a cross platform mobile app. Technologies used included PhoneGap and the Google maps API.

Technology I have experience working with:

Python: Django, Scrapy, Celery, Flask

JavaScript: *ES7*, *React*, *Reflux* **iOS / hybrid**: *Swift*, *React Native*

Web design: Sass

Infrastructure: Vagrant, Ansible, Webpack

Databases: Postgresql, MongoDB

 $\textbf{Design:}\ Photoshop,\ Illustrator,\ in Design,\ Sketch$

Other: Salesforce marketing automation

Technologies I have worked with in the past:

pHp, Wordpress, ActionScript (Flash), ColdFusion

Education:

Edinburgh College of Art - University of Edinburgh. Visual Communication Graduated 2010